Bell Brothers Collection
Bell Brothers Collection
- Audiotapes
  - Benny Goodman Carnegie Hall Concert, 10/06/1939; bell_brothers_tapes_028; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 2)
  - Benny Goodman Swing into Spring - TV, 04/10/1959; bell_brothers_tapes_029; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 3)
  - Benny Goodman, Cab Calloway, and Al Jolson broadcasts, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_004; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 1)
  - Benny Monten, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_553; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 40)
  - Berg, Wozzeck Metropolitan, (Part 1), 03/14/1959; bell_brothers_tapes_038; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 3)
  - Berg, Wozzeck Metropolitan, (Part 2), 03/14/1959; bell_brothers_tapes_039; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 3)
  - Berlioz: Trojans At Carthage, (Part 2), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_118; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 9)
  - Best Food Forward Film, Lucille Ball, (Part 1), 1943; bell_brothers_tapes_033; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 3)
  - Best Food Forward Film, Lucille Ball, (Part 2), 1943; bell_brothers_tapes_034; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 3)
  - Betly, Donizetti; Gianni-Schicchi, Puccini; Das Buch mit den Sieben Sigeln, Schmidt, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_336; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 24)
  - Beyond Blue Horizon; A Foreign Affair, M. Dietrich; Meistersinger, Bayreuth Festival, 1961; bell_brothers_tapes_706; 1/4 inch audio tape (Tray 2)
  - Beyond Blue Horizon; A Foreign Affair, M. Dietrich; Meistersinger, Bayreuth Festival, 1961; bell_brothers_tapes_707; 1/4 inch audio tape (Tray 2)
  - Big Broadcast of 1932 Film Bing Crosby, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_025; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 2)
  - Big Pond, Fred Astaire, 1930; bell_brothers_tapes_334; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 24)
  - Billie Holiday Second City; Elisir DAmore (Donizetti), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_638; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 46)
  - Bing Crosby, 10/05/1960; bell_brothers_tapes_220; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 16)
  - Bing Crosby - Pablo Casals - Bartok, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_449; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 33)
  - Bing Crosby and Perry Como - Born to Dance, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_094; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 7)
  - Bing Crosby and Perry Como - Born to Dance; When you're in love, Grace Moore, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_095; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 7)
  - Bing Crosby TV; Take Me Out to the Ball Game, 09/29/1959; bell_brothers_tapes_689; 1/4 inch audio tape (Tray 1)
  - Bing Crosby TV; Take Me Out to the Ball Game, 09/29/1959; bell_brothers_tapes_690; 1/4 inch audio tape (Tray 1)
  - Bing Crosby; Andres Segovia; Hemingway, PM Bidu Sayao; Phalguni, Mandir, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_414; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 30)
  - Birth of the Blues; For whom the Bell Tolls; Pineapple Poll; The Fleets In, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_102; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 8)
  - Bluebeards Castle; Miraculous Mandarin, Bartok; C. Siepi; Sleepy Beauty; Firestone Hour; Burnett and Preston; Maurice Chevalier, 02/20/1963; bell_brothers_tapes_555; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 40)
  - Blues In the Night Khovantschina (Moussorgsky) - Dylan Thomas, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_483; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 35)
  - Bohemian Girl Nixon-Krustchev- L.V. Cunningham; Der Wildschutz (Lortzing) Aunt Molly Jackson; Holiday in Mexico Jane Powell, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_139; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 10)
  - Boris Godonouv - Moussorgsky - Metropolitan Nuremberg Film of the Trials, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_592; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 43)
  - Boris Goudonouff, Metropolitan - G. London, 01/07/1961; bell_brothers_tapes_103; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 8)
  - Boris Goudonouff, Metropolitan - G. London, 01/07/1961; bell_brothers_tapes_104; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 8)
  - Borst Christoff - Rev. R. Abernathy- Savritri (Holst) - Having a Wonderful Time - Carmen - Rhythm on the Range - The Deserteur (Monsigny), 03/14/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_403; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 29)
  - Boys from Syracuse - Justice Warren - Jan Peerce - Perry Como, 04/18/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_396; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 29)
  - Break of day, Jones; Marc Connely; Helen Morgan; Fanny Brice; George Gershwin; Clark and Cullough; Texas Guinan, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_057; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 5)
  - Brecht Festival: Happy end; Herr Puntilla; Mother; Courage Seven Deadly sins, Memorial, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_093; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 7)
  - Bride From Messina, Fibich; Dalibor, Smetana; Broadway Through a Keyhole, Russ Columbo; Mad About Music, Deanna Durbin, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_573; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 41)
  - Broadway Melody, Film, Astaire - Eleanor Powell, (Part 1), 1940; bell_brothers_tapes_041; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 3)
  - Broadway Melody, Film, Astaire - Eleanor Powell, (Part 2), 1940; bell_brothers_tapes_042; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 3)
  - Bundle of Joy (Eddie Fisher - Debbie Reynolds), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_132; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 10)
  - By the light of the Silvery Moon - Igor Stravinsky - Merchant of Venice (Mario Tedesco) Mario Sammarco- King Kongs (South African Jazz) Opera, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_314; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 23)
  - Cabin in the Sky - Princess Came Across Film Carolina White - Seldom Heard Lucia Perry Como; Having a Wonderful Time, 03/14/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_402; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 29)
  - Capt. Carlson; Gen. G. Marshall; Al Smith; H. Willis - Symphonies; T. Lemnitz; M. Fleta; H. Roswaenge; L. Bori, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_648; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 47)
  - Carl Nielsen; E. German Composers; Hitler; American Civil War, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_301; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 22)
  - Casals at White House, J. Tourel, Mary Garden; Josef Lhevinne, Jazz TV, 11/26/1961; bell_brothers_tapes_385; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 28)
  - Cavalleria Rusticana Eileen Farrell; Don Juan in Hell (Part 1), 12/03/1960; bell_brothers_tapes_163; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 12)
  - Chi dellalturi si - veste - Cimarosa Mussolini - Vanni - Marcoux, Bass, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_632; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 46)
  - Christa Ludwig; Arlechino, Busoni; Ivan IV, Bizet; Magic Violin, EGK; John McCormack; L. Olivier; L. Slezak, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_524; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 38)
  - Christus, Liszt; Pope John XXIII; Voice of Firestone; Symphonic Works; Great Mass, Mozart; Benny Moten; Emilio De Gogorza; Grace Kelly, Biog., 04/14/1963; bell_brothers_tapes_625; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 45)
  - Chu Chin Chow; Pieces of Eight, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_085; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 7)
  - Chu Chin Chow; Stanley Green, 02/01/1961; bell_brothers_tapes_080; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 6)
  - Cleopatra, Rodgers; Hart, CBS, 1937; bell_brothers_tapes_653; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 47)
  - Collegiate Film Di Natali (Barber) Miscellaneous Personalities, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_485; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 35)
  - Como, TV; Salvador Dali; Sincerely Yours; Libearce, Crimson Piarte, Menuhin; Beyond the Fringe, 12/26/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_570; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 41)
  - Coney Island -- Conneticut Yankee; College Humor; Astronaut Glenn - P. Como, 03/21/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_401; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 29)
  - Conference at Belgrade - 1961 percussion - Harp Philosophy in America, 03/17/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_272; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 20)
  - Consort of Musicke - Japanese Poems - Il Filosof Di Campagna (Galuppi) - Losteria Portughese Cherubini, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_291; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 21)
  - Corwell - Barber - Tansman - Webern - Martinu - Allegra - Jommelli - Adam - castel. - Tedesco - Haydn - Japanese, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_488; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 35)
  - Crescendo (Cherubini) - Ginevra Degli Almieri (Pergallo); Lodoiska (Conclusion) (Cherubini), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_667; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 48)
  - Cristoforo Columbo; Springtime in the Rockies, Mrs. F. D. R.; Paris Honeymoon; Lotte Lehmann, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_532; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 38)
  - Crosby Show; Harry James; Lenox Ave Suite, 03/29/1950; 08/14/1939; bell_brothers_tapes_655; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 47)
  - Crosby; Radio, Kraft; Benny Goodman, Radio; N. Melba, Farewell; C. Muzio, Tosca; Rommel, 03/06/1941; 03/03/1938; 04/02/1942; 12/18/1937; 01/18/1938; 03/31/1938; bell_brothers_tapes_607; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 44)
  - Czar has his Picture Taken, Weill; Protagonist, Weill; Laudes Evangelii, Bucchi; Artists and Models; Salute for Three, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_408; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 30)
  - D. Oistrakh (Festival) Trovatore; E. Coates - Arnold May Night (Rimsky Korsakoff) - T. Schipa Licia Albanese; G. Malcom (Interview on harpsichord), 05/19/1942; 10/06/1933; 08/02/1951; bell_brothers_tapes_660; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 48)
  - Da Romanza Di Salome, Lupi, E. Schumann-Heink, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_202; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 15)
  - DAMES Conclusion; Hoffa; Kennedy, Bobby; Krustchev; Nixon (Part 2), 1934; "bell_brothers_tapes_019 "; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 2)
  - DAMES Film - DICK POWELL (Part 1), 1934; "bell_brothers_tapes_018 "; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 2)
  - Damnation of Faust, Berlioz; Aristotle; An Ideal Husband, Wilde; On Harmfulness of Tobacco, Chekhov; French Festivals of Bois and Nice; Hashlemere Festival, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_628; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 25)
  - Danny Kaye- TV, 10/30/1960; bell_brothers_tapes_224; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 16)
  - Dardanus (Rameau) Berwald - Palestrina- Otello (Rossini)- Richard, Lion Hearted (gretry) - TeDeum (Dvorak), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_309; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 23)
  - Daughter of the regiment, Donizetty, Lily Pons, Metropolitan Opera Broadcast, 12/28/1940; bell_brothers_tapes_067; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 5)
  - David and Igor Oistrakh-Prague Festival; Will Rogers - The Climax, 1961; bell_brothers_tapes_270; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 20)
  - Dean Martin - Frank Sinatra, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_219; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 16)
  - Dean Martin TV, Sinatra; Rooney guests, 11/03/1959; bell_brothers_tapes_040; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 3)
  - Death of a Salesman, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_236; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 17)
  - Dedication of CBS Latin-American Network Network; Town Crier; Alexander Woolcott Hit Parade, 05/19/1942; 10/06/1933; 08/02/1951; bell_brothers_tapes_659; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 48)
  - Deidemia, Handel; Mattia Battistini; AFRS Lib. Series; Watt Tyler, Busch; McGuire Sisters, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_521; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 38)
  - Demi-Dozen, Review, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_092; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 7)
  - Demon; Young Man with Horn; Smirnov; Das Marienleben, John McCormack, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_505; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 37)
  - Denny Goodman - (Camel Caravan) - Goodman (Hotel Pennsylvania)- Goodman (Hotel New Yorker), 08/10/1937; 08/17/1937; 08/24/1937; 08/31/1937; 10/13/1937; 10/16/1937; 10/20/1937; 10/21/1937; 10/30/1937; 11/04/1937; 11/06/1937; bell_brothers_tapes_612; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 44)
  - Der Holz dleb; J. Metternisch; Die Wanderinsel; Die Freunde Von Salamanka; Xerxes, Handel; John McCormack, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_474; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 34)
  - Der Liebe der Daune, R Strauss; Die Egyptische Helena, R. Strauss; Giovanna DArco, Verdi, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_308; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 22)
  - Deseret, Kastle, NBC Opera, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_179; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 13)
  - Desi Halban - Mabel Garrison, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_269; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 20)
  - Desire Dietrich - Documentary Not So Long Ago, 10/30/1960; bell_brothers_tapes_226; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 17)
  - Destry Rides Again; Gangs All Here; Symphony No. 2, Enesco, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_498; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 36)
  - Devil Dogs of the Air; Justice, Charles Evans, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_500; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 36)
  - Dialogues of the Carmelites, Poulenc; Mother Courage, Brecht, Vienna Choir Boys; Joan Sutherland; Adelina Patti; Tiana Lemnitz, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_606; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 44)
  - Didon, Piccini; Pirata; Gazzetta, Rossini, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_142; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 11)
  - Die Gotterdammerung; Siegfried (Covent Garden), 1959; bell_brothers_tapes_370; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 27)
  - Die Schweigsame Frau (R. Strauss) Radamisto (Handel), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_259; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 19)
  - Die Tote Stadt; Ernani, Delius, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_535; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 39)
  - Die Walkure, Bayreuth Festival, (Part 1), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_122; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 9)
  - Die Walkure, Bayreuth Festival, (Part 2), 1960; bell_brothers_tapes_123; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 9)
  - Die Walkure, Wagner, Metropolitan Opera, 02/20/1960; bell_brothers_tapes_090; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 7)
  - Die Walkure, Wagner, Metropolitan Opera, 02/20/1960; bell_brothers_tapes_091; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 7)
  - Dimples; Der Betrogene Kadi; Serva Padrona; Euryanthe, Villa Lobos, Mitropolous, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_504; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 36)
  - Doctor Turned Into Glass, Vlad; Charlie Parker, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_325; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 24)
  - Doktor Faust, Busoni, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_147; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 11)
  - Don Carlo, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_670; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 48)
  - Don Carlo (Verdi), 11/11/1950; bell_brothers_tapes_669; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 48)
  - Don Carlo (Verdi); Salsburg Festival, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_159; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 12)
  - Don Carlo (Verdi); Salsburg Festival, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_160; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 12)
  - Don Carlo, Verdi, Texaco-Metropolitan Opera; Radio Network, 03/07/1963; bell_brothers_tapes_682; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 49)
  - Don Giovanni Mozart - NBC Opera, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_130; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 10)
  - Don Juan in Hell; Song of the Islands, Billie Holiday; Lively Ones, TV; Three Penny opera; Miscellaneous Operatic Singers, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_514; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 37)
  - Don Juan Manara (Goosens) Kiebura; Gorin - etc.; I Cvalieri Ekebu (Zandonai), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_391; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 28)
  - Double or Nothin; Lucky Me - P.M.E. College Rhythm - In the Well (Brodek), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_392; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 28)
  - Dr. Jekyll and Mt. Hyde - Von Wurtzler - Harpist - I Capuleti E I Montecchi (Bellini), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_266; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 19)
  - Dr. R. C. Baker; Christian Science, 02/03/1963; 02/24/1963; 03/03/1963; 03/10/1963; bell_brothers_tapes_564; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 41)
  - Dream Ridiculous Man (Dostoyevsky) - B. Beardsless, Sop. Perry Como, 03/27/1963; 04/13/1963; bell_brothers_tapes_588; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 42)
  - Dubrovsky E. Napravnik - Lodoletta (Mascagni) - Death of a Wombat (George English)- Kirsten Flagstad- Ethel Waters- Bing Crosby Film, 04/18/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_398; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 29)
  - Duel (Paisiello) Concerto a cinque (Paisiello) - Gospel Songs - Anima E Corpo (Cavalieri) - Town Hall - Chinese Work Felicia Sanders - Stand Up and Cheer, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_313; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 23)
  - E. Carron; Dr. Barker; S. Henderson; Haydn; Spohr; Suder; Zolner; Schreker; Kozeluh; Danzi; Wanhal, etc., 04/21/1963; 04/28/1963; bell_brothers_tapes_646; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 47)
  - Earl K. Long - Musical Comedies (Readers Digest), 06/15/1963; 06/16/1963; bell_brothers_tapes_603; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 44)
  - Early Opera Singers, Raoul Guillaume, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_503; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 36)
  - Early Operatic Singers, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_487; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 35)
  - Early Operatic Singers, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_499; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 36)
  - Early Singers On GandT, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_454; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 33)
  - Easter Parade Astaire - Garland, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_237; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 17)
  - Easy to Wed Welcome Stranger King of Burlesque Fabulous Dorseys, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_129; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 10)
  - Eichmann Trial, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_327; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 24)
  - Eichmann Trial, Ben Gurion; Abba Eban, Rockwell, 04/12/1961; bell_brothers_tapes_326; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 24)
  - Eileen Farrell; Nan Merriman: Fisher-Diskau; Cardinal Spellman; Eichman Trial; Bor, Bas., undated; bell_brothers_tapes_135; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 10)
  - Elisa, Cherubini, (Part 1), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_181; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 13)
  - Elisa, Cherubini, (Part 2), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_182; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 13)
  - Elisir DAmore (Donizetti) Metropolitan, 12/24/1960; bell_brothers_tapes_167; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 12)
  - Ellington with Orch. Cleveland Symphony - Grand Hotel - Works by Eldin Burton (Carnegie Hall), 1932; bell_brothers_tapes_587; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 42)
  - Ellington, Night at the Opera; Three Smart Girls; Gentlemen Prefer Blondes; VanCliburn, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_550; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 40)
  - Embers Beckett - Square Duras, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_229; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 17)
  - Emperor Waltz Bing Crosby, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_212; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 16)
  - Encyclical of Pope John XXIII - Saul (Handel); Du Barry was a Lady (Film), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_633; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 46)
  - Ernani, Metropolitan; German Requiem, 12/01/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_510; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 37)
  - Ethel Merman - TV, 11/24/1959; "bell_brothers_tapes_023 "; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 2)
  - Eubie Blake and Noble Sissle; Thanks for Everything; Vienna Festival, D. D. Eisenhower, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_305; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 22)
  - Euryanthe (Weber) Miserere (Jommell) Psalm XV (Marcello) Fairy Prince (Arne) La Cenerentola (Rossini), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_310; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 23)
  - Every Night At 8 Como - Tenth Symphony by Mahler - Penelope (Faure) - Hulda (Franck) (Conclusion), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_369; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 27)
  - Everybody sing; The Warrior, Rogers; Dewey - Kurz- Mayr; The Great Gilbert and Sullivan; Nuremberg Trails; Le Coq D'Or, Patrice Munsel, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_176; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 13)
  - Exception and The Rule Brecht - Desau - Mass of Gran Liszt- D. Lipatti - Mozart Concerto #21, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_278; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 20)
  - F. D. R. Biography; Rehearsals; Walter; Beecham; Serafin; Oratorios: Historia di Ezechia; Historia di Abraham and Isaac; Il Pianto dei Dannati; All by G. Carissimi, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_421; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 31)
  - F.L. Wright - Duke Ellington - Great Ziegfeld Perry Como, 02/21/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_405; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 29)
  - Falstaff; Norma; Oedipus Rex; Stoessel; Deems Taylor, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_299; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 22)
  - Fats Waller - Sinatra and E. Hodges - Mildred Bailey - Sinatra (Major Bowes Amateur) A. Schiotz, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_430; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 31)
  - Faust, Film; Lamplighters Melgerberg Concert; Quattro Pezzi Sacri, Verdi; Salvador Dali; PM TV, Marcel Wittrsch, 01/30/1961; bell_brothers_tapes_381; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 28)
  - Faust, Gounod, Metropolitan Opera, Bjoerling, 12/19/1960; bell_brothers_tapes_207; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 15)
  - Fedra Paisiello Fedra Pizetti Royal Wedding If I'm Lucky, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_373; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 27)
  - Fervaal, DIndy; Moniusko and Other Polish Composers; Robert the Devil, Mayerbeer, Vocals, Toscanini, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_559; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 40)
  - Fidel Castro, Renata Tebaldi: Gay Divorcee, (Part 1), 02/02/1959; bell_brothers_tapes_012; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 1)
  - Fidelio (Beethoven), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_161; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 12)
  - Fidelio Metropolitan (Beethoven), 02/13/1960; "bell_brothers_tapes_136 "; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 10)
  - Fidelio Metropolitan (Beethoven), 02/13/1960; "bell_brothers_tapes_137 "; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 10)
  - Fidelio Metropolitan (Beethoven), 02/13/1960; "bell_brothers_tapes_138 "; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 10)
  - Fidelio NBC Opera - Beethoven, 11/08/1959; "bell_brothers_tapes_024 "; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 2)
  - Fidelio; Wright and Sandburg, Prague Festival, Bartok; Christa Luddwig; Carmen Duets, 10/05/1961; bell_brothers_tapes_306; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 22)
  - Fings Ain't Wot they used to be:; Lock up your daughters, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_088; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 7)
  - Firestone -Real Thing - Khovanschina - J.B. Priestley Schumann - Berg - Schoenberg - Brahms, 1937; bell_brothers_tapes_580; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 42)
  - Fischer; Dieskau; Kostelanetz; Curtin; Taft; Como; Rushing; Petite Messe Solennele, Rossini; Pavolska; Ponselle; Telva; Martinelli; Every Days Holiday, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_562; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 41)
  - Flanders Concert MacLeish and Doren; Jones, 08/03/1961; bell_brothers_tapes_494; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 36)
  - Fledermaus, Metropolitan; Bob Hope TV Awards; Easter Liturgy, Monks Choir, 04/13/1963; 04/14/1963; bell_brothers_tapes_617; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 45)
  - Flying Down to Rio - Lulu Belle Schoene Muellerin (Schubert) - Harry S. Truman - G.A. Nasser - Variety Show Sonny Terry - Brownie McGhee, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_282; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 21)
  - Flying Dutchman Miscellaneous Personalities -, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_479; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 35)
  - Follow the Boys; Siberia, Gordano; H. Rehkemper, Bar. John McCormack; Aldous Huxley; Beet Generation; LUccellatrice, N. Jommelli, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_506; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 37)
  - Forgotten Music: Hahn - Juon - Raff- Locatelli- Rubinstein - Malipieoro, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_406; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 29)
  - Forgotten Music; Spohr, Ropartz; Sgambati; Jacob; Rubinstein, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_507; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 37)
  - Forza del Destino, Metropolitan, Frieda Hempel; W. B. Yeats; Bruno Hauptmannll, 12/30/1961; bell_brothers_tapes_410; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 30)
  - Forza Del Destino; Verdi, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_131; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 10)
  - Fra Diavolo, Auber; Jerry Lewis, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_329; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 24)
  - Frank Sinatra - Elvis Presley, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_242; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 18)
  - Frank Sinatra - Mrs. F. D. Roosevelt; Lena Horne, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_117; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 9)
  - Frank Sinatra - TV With Ella Fitzgerald, 12/13/1959; bell_brothers_tapes_006; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 1)
  - FRANK SINATRA TV - Crosby- D. Martin, 10/19/1959; "bell_brothers_tapes_026 "; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 2)
  - Fred Allen Roaring 20's TV, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_035; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 3)
  - Fred Astaire - Evening with Fred Astaire TV, 10/17/1958; "bell_brothers_tapes_043 "; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 4)
  - Fred Astaire - TV, 09/28/1960; bell_brothers_tapes_234; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 17)
  - FRED ASTAIRE Another Evening with Fred Astaire TV, 11/04/1959; "bell_brothers_tapes_027 "; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 2)
  - Frieda Hempel - Frieda Leider - Lilli Lehmann - Van Rooy - Van Dyck - K. Scheidemantel, ten., undated; bell_brothers_tapes_453; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 33)
  - G. C. Menotti, Maria Golovin NBC (Part 1), 03/08/1958; bell_brothers_tapes_008; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 1)
  - G. C. Menotti, Maria Golovin NBC (Part 2), 03/08/1958; bell_brothers_tapes_009; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 1)
  - Gambler Prokofier Lo Sposo Deluso (Mozart) - F.D.R.; Lucio Silla (Mozart) - La partita aPugni (Tosatti) - Bertrand Russell, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_356; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 26)
  - Gay Divorcee, (Part 2), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_013; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 1)